A Guide to the Harry C. Ficklen Papers
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #301
Harry C. Ficklen Papers 1860-1935
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
301
ca. 100 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift
Container List
- Articles by Harry C. Ficklen, n.d.; (2 folders) (Box Box 1)
- Correspondence of Harry C. Ficklen, 1860, 1866-1931 (Box Box 1)
- Essays on the Jury System by Harry C. Ficklen, n.d.; (3 folders) (Box Box 1)
- Essays, Anecdotes, Notes and Signature by Harry C. Ficklen, 1885,1897,1914,1923, n.d. (Box Box 1)
- Humorous Articles by Harry C. Ficklen, 1895 (Box Box 1)
- John F. Ficklen's Statements of Account with Slaughter Company, 1861-1862 (Box Box 1)
- Miscellaneous, 1916, n.d. (Box Box 1)
- Poems by Harry C. Ficklen, 1896-1897, 1900-1936, n.d.; (2 folders) (Box Box 2)
- Speech: "Am I My Brother's Keeper?" by Harry C. Ficklen, 1921 (Box Box 2)
- Unsigned Poems and Poems By Other Authors, 1931, n.d. (Box Box 2)